http://www.red-gate.com/website/legal

OVERVIEW Compliant Database DevOpsBY NEED Standardize team-based development Automate database deployments Monitor performance and availability Protect and preserve dataBY ROLEDevelopmentOperationsIT ManagementEnterprise leadershipBY INDUSTRYTechFinanceU.S. FederalHealthcareManaged Service ProvidersLegal information – privacy and cancellationsPrivacy noticeRedgate (which means Red Gate Software Limited and its subsidiaries) respects your privacy. All information you give us is held with the utmost care and security.Please take time to review this privacy policy as it sets out our privacy practices and tells you how your personal information will be treated by us. We do not sell, rent or loan any identifiable information regarding our customers to any third party. Only in the circumstances described within this Privacy Policy would we share your information with any third party.Our use of personal data is in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulations 2016 (GDPR).How we use your informationIf you're visiting our websites, using our products and services, working with any of our teams, meeting us at events or applying for a role with us, this privacy notice sets out what data we collect, and how we use it. It also describes your rights regarding our use of your data.We collect common types of personal information, such as: name, job title, company, industry, postal address, email address, phone number, and your computer's IP address.We will use the personal information provided to us to:Process orders submitted by youIdentify the Redgate 'certified partner' that is best placed to support your software purchase if you cannot purchase directly from us;Customize the service we provide to youAdministrate or otherwise carry out our obligations in relation to any agreement you have with usVerify your identity (e.g. if you participate in any promotions administered by us)Anticipate and resolve any problems with any goods or services supplied to youCarry out market research and surveysSend you our newsletter, where this is requested by youTrack your engagement with us, including through our website, articles and newslettersUnderstand how you use our products and servicesContact you by telephone and send you follow-up communications relating to your use of software downloaded from our websiteSend you information about our other products and servicesProcess your application if you apply for a role with usThis privacy notice tells you what to expect when Redgate collects personal information. It contains more information about:Visiting our websitesWhen you visit one of our websites, we collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behavior patterns, including through the use of third-party analytics services (such as Google Analytics). We do this to understand how people are using our websites, to manage their operation and to diagnose any problems. We retain these logs for up to three months.We use Hubspot and Marketo to track your engagement with our website, and help give you the most relevant information on our products and solutions. This data is visible to our sales and marketing teams. We keep data you have provided to us, for example if you fill out a form on our website, for the duration of our commercial relationship with you.We also use third-party services to help us identify visitors to our website to improve the way we offer our products and services.We rely on the lawful basis of legitimate interests to process this data.Our website search is powered by Google. Search queries and results are logged anonymously to help us improve our website and search functionality. No user-specific data is collected by either Redgate or any third party.How we use cookiesYour web browser allows you to control whether cookies can be stored by our websites. However, disabling cookies will prevent certain parts of our websites from working correctly. Your web browser’s documentation has more information on controlling cookie behavior.We use cookies on our websites to:Maintain your active sessionStore your preferencesTrack the success of our marketing and advertising campaignsAnalyze the way people use our websitesGather data on how our websites are performingCommunity newslettersWe send newsletters for SQL Server Central and Simple-Talk and Amazon Simple Email Service. We gather statistics around email opening and interaction using industry-standard technologies, including tracking pixels, to analyze the performance or email campaigns. We use data about your interactions with our emails as an indicator of your interest in our products. We may also use your interaction with our previous newsletters to send you more appropriate information in the future.We rely on your consent to send you Simple Talk and SQL Server Central newsletters.You can opt out of receiving these newsletters at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link in these emails, or by managing your email preferences. For SQL Server Central, manage your preferences here.Contacting us on social mediaRedgate maintains a presence on Twitter, Facebook and LinkedIn. We manage your interactions with us using HubSpot as well as using social media platforms directly.If you send us a message via social media, we may include this in our CRM systems.We process this data on the basis of our legitimate interests.Connecting with our product support teamsIf you engage with our support teams, we may ask you to provide additional information to help us assist you (like diagnostic logs). We may share this internally with our teams to support you and to enable them to reproduce and fix product issues. We may also cross reference your interactions with us in order to understand the customer journey, improve our self-help articles and to give you the best support experience.Some of our products also include feedback mechanisms such as live chat. If you’re signed into the product, we’ll see your name and email address when you chat to us. Any information you send to us in the chat session will be shared with our product development and support teams.Processing this data is necessary to allow us to fulfill your support contract with us.Recording telephone callsWe record some calls for training and quality purposes to help us evaluate our performance and better understand the needs of our customers. If you live in the USA and two-party consent is required, we’ll let you know we’re recording the call at the start.We rely on legitimate interests as the lawful basis for processing this data.Information sent to us when you use our productsOur products send usage and fault reporting information to us. We use this to:Measure how many people are using the different versions of our products, and the different features within themUnderstand the environments in which our products are used (for example, the operating system version, SQL Server version, the amount of system memory and screen resolutions)Measure the success of our sales and marketing operationsGuide product development decisions and improve our productsAssist you in your evaluation, purchasing, and renewal of our productsCompare your usage of our products against the licenses you've purchasedWe use your basic environment and high-level usage data in conjunction with your records in our marketing and CRM systems. Your use of individual features is submitted anonymously and is not linked to your identity.Some of our products allow you to submit error reports if something goes wrong. These contain logs and other diagnostic data, and you can choose to include your contact details and any additional information you think may be useful. Our support and development teams use this data to improve our products.If you choose not to include diagnostic data with an error report, an anonymous record of the type of error which occurred will be sent. This allows us to measure how many of our customers experience errors and prioritise our focus for product development.Automatically-sent usage reporting data is processed on the basis of our legitimate interests. If you choose to submit error reports, we rely on your consent to process this data. You can withdraw your consent at any time, by emailing privacy@red-gate.com.Applying for a role with usIf you apply for a role at Redgate, we will use the information you provide to assess your application.If you are unsuccessful in your application, we will remove your data after 6 months. We may ask your permission to keep your details on file in our talent pool.We use a third party, ICIMS, to manage our recruitment process. Their privacy policy is available here.We process data relating to your application on the basis of our legitimate interests. We also have a legal obligation to check you have the right to work in the country where you are applying to join us.Sharing your information with other partiesRedgate uses select organizations to help us process data which helps us deliver our products and services to you. We will not sell any data regarding your use of our products or services except as part of a reorganization or a sale of the assets of Redgate, and we will ensure that your privacy continues to be protected.If you're a customer, potential customer, or you otherwise have a commercial relationship with Redgate, you can find the current list of organizations here.Joining our Slack instancesSome of our product teams use Slack to work with customers to guide the development of our products, and get feedback on features we're planning or developing.If you join one of these instances, your username and any messages or files you post in public channels will be visible to teams within Redgate and any other customers who have joined the channels you're in. Some channels may be private channels created for your organization; any messages or files you post in these will be visible to your colleagues and Redgate teams in that channel.Our product development Slack channels have a message history of 180 days, after which messages are automatically deleted. Some EAP Slack instances (separate to redgate.slack.com) may have longer retention policies if the development of these products is expected to span a longer duration.Some of our Sales teams may also offer to collaborate with you on Slack. If you choose to do this, you will be invited to a private channel with appropriate colleagues from your company and selected Redgate employees. Messages in this Slack team will be deleted after 180 days.If you wish to delete your account on one of these instances, you should deactivate your account in Slack, then contact us at privacy@red-gate.com. This will remove your profile information; any messages or files you have posted will remain.Participating in Redgate UniversityIf you use our Redgate University content, we will identify you by the email address you sign in with so we can track your progress through the courses we offer, provide you with recognition of your achievements, and grant you access to content based on any Redgate licenses you have purchased or been assigned.Your colleagues who manage your organisation's licenses may invite you to use Redgate University content. If you wish to delete your Redgate University account, contact us at privacy@red-gate.com.We process this data on the basis of our legitimate interests.Transferring your information outside of the European Economic AreaIn order to provide a global service, we transfer information to Red Gate Software Inc. and our service providers situated outside the European Economic Area [EEA], and it may be processed by staff operating outside the EEA. When we do this, we take steps to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected in accordance with EU data protection law.Your rightsUnder the GDPR, you have rights as an individual which you can exercise in relation to the information we hold about you:Confirmation of personal data that is being processedAccess to your personal dataOther supplementary information as referred to (the information provided in our privacy policy)If you object to the way we are processing your data, or would like us to erase your personal data, contact privacy@red-gate.com. If you have purchased products from us, we may need to keep some of your data (for example, records of your purchases) to comply with our legal obligations.Complaints and queriesRedgate tries to meet the highest standards when collecting and using personal information. We take complaints very seriously. If you feel our collection or use of information is unfair, misleading or inappropriate, we encourage you to bring this to our attention. We also welcome any suggestions for improving our procedures.If you have any questions regarding this policy, or wish to make a complaint about the way we’ve handled your personal information, contact privacy@red-gate.com.If you are unhappy with how we have used your data, you can complain to a supervisory authority. In the UK, this is the Information Comissioner's Office.Reporting security issuesIf you become aware of a security vulnerability in any of Redgate's products, services or websites, contact security@red-gate.com.We encourage the responsible disclosure of security issues, and will act quickly on any vulnerabilities reported. We will not take legal action against you if you:Provide us with the information needed to reproduce and validate the vulnerabilityAvoid violating the privacy of our customers, staff and other usersAvoid the destruction of data, or degradation of our servicesDo not modify or access data that is not your ownGive us a reasonable time to address the issue before making any information publicChanges to this privacy policyWe regularly review our privacy policy. This policy was last updated on 6thth August 2020.Questions about data privacyRedgate is the data controller for the information you provide unless otherwise stated. If you have any queries about the process or how we handle your information, contact privacy@red-gate.com.You can also write to us at:Compliance ManagerRed Gate Software LimitedNewnham HouseCambridge Business ParkCambridgeCB4 0WZUnited KingdomCancellationsIn compliance with the Consumer Contracts (Information, Cancellation and Additional Charges) Regulations 2013, you have the right to cancel an order within 14 days of purchase.To cancel, please complete our cancellation form, and send it to Red Gate Software Ltd by post, fax, or email.Download model cancellation form (PDF)LegalRed Gate Software Ltd. (No. 3857576) was incorporated on 12/10/1999 under UK law and, where applicable, complies with all UK laws and regulations.Red Gate Software Inc. was incorporated on 21/1/2011, under the laws of the State of California (US) and, where applicable, complies with all federal and state laws and regulations.
